The Saint Lukas train doesn’t accept passengers — it accepts only the sick.
圣卢卡斯号列车不接载乘客——它只接收病人。
The Saint Lukas is one of five government-sponsored medical trains that travel to remote towns in central and eastern Russia.
圣卢卡斯号是五列由政府资助的医疗列车之一，这些列车开往俄罗斯中部和东部的偏远城镇。
Each stop lasts an average of two days, and during that time the doctors and nurses on board provide rural populations with basic medical care, X-ray scans and prescriptions.
每一站平均停留两天，在此期间，车上的医生和护士为农村居民提供基本医疗服务和X光检查，并开具处方。
“People started queuing to make an appointment early in the morning,” says Emile Ducke, a German photographer who traveled with the staff of the Saint Lukas on a two-week trip in November through the vast regions of Krasnoyarsk and Khakassia.
“人们一大早就开始排队预约，”德国摄影师埃米尔·杜克说。11月，他随圣卢卡斯号的工作人员进行了为期两周的旅行，穿越克拉斯诺亚尔斯克和哈卡斯的广袤地区。
Russia’s public health care service has been in serious need of modernization.
俄罗斯的公共医疗服务一直迫切需要现代化。
The government has struggled to come up with measures to address the problem, particularly in the poorer, rural areas east of the Volga River, including arranging doctor’s appointments by video chat and expanding financial aid programs to motivate doctors to practice medicine in remote parts of the country like Krasnoyarsk.
政府一直在苦苦思索解决这一问题的办法，尤其是在伏尔加河以东较贫困的农村地区，措施包括安排医生通过视频聊天问诊，以及扩大经济援助项目，激励医生到克拉斯诺亚尔斯克这样的偏远地区行医。
The annual arrival of the Saint Lukas is another attempt to improve the situation.
圣卢卡斯号一年一度的到来，是为改善这一状况所做的又一次尝试。
For 10 months every year, the train stops at about eight stations over two weeks, before returning to the regional capital to refuel and restock.
每年有10个月，列车会用两周时间停靠大约8个站点，然后返回地区首府加油、补给。
Then it starts all over again the next month.
到了下个月，它又从头再来。
Most stations wait about a year between visits.
大多数站点要等大约一年才能迎来下一次到访。
Doctors see up to 150 patients every day.
医生们每天要诊治多达150名病人。
The train’s equipment allows for basic checkups.
借助列车上的设备，可以进行基本的身体检查。
“I was very impressed by the doctors and their assistants working and living in such little space but still staying focused and very concerned,” says Ducke.
“医生和他们的助手在如此狭小的空间里工作和生活，却依然保持专注、十分尽心，这让我印象深刻，”杜克说。
“They were the best chance for many rural people to get the treatment they want.”
“对许多农村居民来说，要得到自己想要的治疗，最好的机会就是他们。”